Bradley **Schwarz**

□ 704-241-2153 | ■ bradleyschwarz1@gmail.com

Summary

Full Stack Engineer currently looking for a new role. I have 7+ years experience specializing in frontend development, interface design, and making complex systems easy to use. I enjoy looking at the fundamental aspects of a product's design by examining its meaning and the purpose it brings to the world. The answers are discovered through the interplay of form and function.

Work Experience _____

Thetacore Lehi, Utah (remote)

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

April 2021 - June 2024

Sept 2016 - April 2021

- Participated in fast paced iterative early startup product development and brainstorming
- Lead a standup meeting for a small team of frontend engineers
- Participated in prototyping an intensive caching Vue is progressive web application
- Assisted with the design and development of a Administration dotnet application
- · Implemented numerous product features relating to chat, team management, and user connection for a Blazor Dotnet application
- Assisted with developing an automation test suite utilizing microsoft playwright
- Prototyped and developed graphical visualizations for product needs

Aqueti Inc. Durham, NC

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

- Lead a small team to create a distributed ecosystem for viewing, and maintaining Aqueti camera systems Designed, built, and deployed Vue progressive web application for administrative management of Aqueti camera systems
- Designed an overall service architecture and pipelines for supplying high quality streaming to browsers using GStreamer and WebRTC
- Implemented Socket.io API layer for Aqueti OS allowing for cross platform applications integration
- · Participated in the design and implementation of a scalable image acquisition and and compositing system consisting of high resolution multisensor camera arrays with distributed rendering and storage

Education

North Carolina State University

Raleigh, NC

B.S. IN COMPUTER SCIENCE AND ENGINEERING

Aug. 2012 - May. 2016

• Minor in Cognitive Science

Extracurricular Activity

Artist Blacksmith Durham, NC

June 2021 - Present

- Research historic ironwork techniques and methods
- · Create artistic ironwork through iteritive process development

Cognitive Psychology Research NC STATE HUMAN FACTORS AND ERGONOMICS

Raleigh, NC Jan. 2018 - Feb. 2019

• Designed and implemented study to determine correlations between mindfulness and aspects of cognition

• Designed study to examine the potential negative effects of mindfulness and automated tasks

Skills_

HARK AND HEED

Back-end REST API, Socket.io, Flask, QT, Dotnet

Front-end HTML5, Vue, React, Vuetify, Bootstrap, Dotnet

Programming Python, JavaScript, C, C++, CSS, C#